hey what's up my name is jeremi Kowski
and I want to teach you how to live a
better life if you're a business owner
this video is going to be something
that's going to show you some of the
lessons that I wish I knew when I got
started in my own business that you can
apply yourself and for those of you that
are wondering who I am I've been in the
online marketing space helping business
owners for the last 21 years scale to
make tens of millions of dollars in the
coaching course and seminar space we
used to do DVD and CD products back in
the day and I built multiple businesses
over $10 million and I want to help you
succeed whether you're just starting out
or you have been in the space for a long
time how do you get more clients and how
do you make things happen something that
comes up in my coaching calls my clients
is how we can actually optimize our
brain and so what I'm going to talk
about here is it's not necessarily a
mindset training but it's something that
I want you to pay attention to when it
comes to how your thinking is processing
information it's related to the
reticular activating system if you don't
know what the particular activating
system is it has to do with that part of
your brain that like when you when you
notice things and you can recognize
opportunities one of the biggest
problems as to why people don't succeed
is they're not recognizing opportunities
they're not seeing things for what they
really are when they show up in their
life and they're and they're waiting for
Perfection they're waiting for things to
be perfect instead of accepting things
for how they are number one which is
going to be powerful for you I'm going
to talk about that in a little bit as
well but also being able to train your
mind to see the best opportunities
instead of striving and working so hard
to make everything perfect and this goes
against the normal thinking in our
brains because we think that the harder
I grip onto how I want things to go the
better they will for me when the reality
is that couldn't be further from the
truth and I have years of experience as
well as work work with thousands of
clients to prove this with evidence that
I'm going to be bringing to you here
today okay and so what we have to look
at is this is that what is the thing
that you want in your life in your
business I need you to get clear on it
well I want to make more money
why and you might say well so I can pay
off my bills why do you want to pay off
your bills well so I can have less
stress well why do you want to have less
stress and now we start getting to the
root cause of it we asked four or five
layers of why I'm sure you've heard of
this if you've been in the personal
development space for a long time maybe
this is the first time you're hearing
this asking multiple layers of why
behind the reason that we want to do
something why do I want to grow my
business why do I want to get more
clients okay and we can really identify
what that root cause issue is we can
start to identify how to fix it now one
of the biggest issues is that our brain
how we tune it is where we focus and so
if I'm watching a movie that's negative
and
dark no wonder the next day I'm focused
so much on how things can go bad in my
life or in my business if I'm reading
content on social media if I'm watching
the news media about who was recently
arrested or or who killed who or things
like that my we used to joke about that
when I was younger you know what was
what do we call the news who killed who
it's not fun but it's funny at the same
time CU it's like that's what the news
reports on is all the negativity and the
Darkness in our world and if you if you
pay attention to negativity the brain
does something very powerful is it looks
for more in that same lane or modality
and so what we have to do is we have to
start to pay attention
to what we want and what we're looking
for and what we're seeking out we have
to set intention in our minds for our
activities if all I focus on is how I
struggle to be able to build my business
I'm
overwhelmed by the things I have to do
that's all we're going to see and then
we're going to see how everything else
is overwhelming and this creates a
vicious cycle that we get
into the way that the reticular
activating system works is very
interesting is that whatever we have in
our life we see more of and it stands
out to us more it's a very unique thing
in our in our in our psychology
if one of the best ways that people
notice it is if you ever buy a model of
a car you notice that everybody who
already has that model of car is driving
you notice your car on the road
everywhere it's like everybody's driving
your car no matter what it is no matter
which car you have and then you sell
that car and it seems like now those
people aren't driving your car anymore
that's exactly what it is it's the brain
focuses more on where it spends its
focus and it notices opportunities more
that way and so when it comes to your
business and your
marketing something that I actually
teach people is that if you can actually
play on in a positive way the reticular
activating system of the clients that
you're trying to reach you can show up
for the very things where they have
their focus and you can actually show in
front of people where they're putting
their focus as far as that goes and
that's really cool because the
algorithms start to amplify this on
social media and advertising and then
now now that we have artificial
intelligence we can use this to even
optimize a lot of these different layers
of these processes which is really
really exciting and fun so let's kind of
dive a little bit deeper into this now
as to how you can use this in your life
and your business number one you have to
shift what you're focusing on if all we
focus on and think about is what can go
wrong and what am I trying to
avoid it's all all we're going to see
and that's and every single situation is
going to play out they've done studies
where the negative shows up twice as
much as the positive and then what ends
up happening is we're replaying either
our memory or the memories and stories
that somebody else has told us and we
make decisions on things that haven't
even happened
yet because of where our mind focus is
and Our intention is on avoiding the bad
stuff from happening Our intention is so
much on avoiding things not happening
the way we don't want them to okay that
stinks it's not a way to be successful
but it's how our brains are naturally
wired and bent towards operating so we
have to be intentional to steer the
thinking in our brain to start to focus
on what we actually want and this
I get it can be difficult especially if
your spouse your family your work your
job the things you're doing every single
day are not in alignment with that and
so you have to learn how to reset your
brain and transition quickly and
compartmentalize from one place to
another and this is one of the most
powerful things that we can learn this
is what billionaire Executives you know
I read the biography of Bob Iger the
executive CEO of
Disney he talks about that his is
probably his best skill is being able to
go from one crazy situation to another
to another and they're so unrelated that
the emotions that he has to go deep into
in each situation would overwhelm
him and yet he's able to Pivot and
switch 30 minutes over here 30 minutes
over here 30 minutes over here and what
that allows you to do is you don't have
to have a lot of build up time to go
into the things that we're doing if
we're on if we're constantly replaying
negativity in our brain we're going to
be like
okay that's all I see that's all that's
happening nothing works for me I've been
at this for 17 years and nothing is
going my
way this is why affirmations actually do
have a positive framework to them it's
not that we're trying to lie to oursel
and convince ourselves of something but
we're actually just trying to align
where our focus is going and then we
start to recognize opportunities that
are within that lane of focus you know
visualization is powerful it's actually
really cool is you can even find
visualization videos on YouTube if
you're doing Fitness you can find
Fitness visualization videos of people
working out in the gym if you're working
in a business you can pull up B like
lifestyle visualization videos of
wealthy people just doing wealthy people
things on on YouTube and it's very
interesting because if you play this
even in the background or you play this
I tried this this morning it was just
kind of fun while I took a shower and it
got me into a different modality of
thinking I find that if I listen to a
podcast from a wealthy business owner
that's making at least $1 to $200
million a year for some reason I start
thinking and coming into alignment with
the way that they communicate and the
way that they talk and I'm not and I'm
not necessarily going to copy or say the
things that they say
I don't want to do that I want to
plagiarize what other people are
saying but I'm thinking as if I was
immersed into their environment as far
as that goes a lot of us our
environments are working against us and
we don't even know a way out because
there's so much fighting against us but
the one thing that nobody can control is
what's going on up in here except for
you and you get to control that based on
where you put your focus I'm not talking
about striving Focus if I got to focus
focus focus I'm not even that great at
that myself but what I do is I tune my
alignment I'm like changing the radio
dial and I'm hello welcome to you
know that was my radio dial right there
but I'm able to tune the radio dial to
the energy or the emotion or the thought
or the experience
or the thing that I'm about to go do and
I use a number of different ways to do
this I can one of the ways I tune my
radio dial is if I'm struggling to have
my thoughts be organized I go clean up
stuff around my house for some reason my
thoughts start to come into alignment
after about 10 15 minutes of cleaning up
something else in my house everything
else starts to get organized in my mind
it's pretty cool if I'm trying to become
creative when it comes to storytelling I
may watch a movie on Netflix some of the
best ways of writing sales copy for your
in pages and your offers and your
Facebook ads and your content come from
storytelling and yet I find so many
people refuse to watch fictional stories
or to read novels I play video games
even because it gets me into a creative
modality because I'm that's where my
focus is now of course too much of that
can't be healthy if I'm cleaning my
whole house all day and I'm not actually
building my business or not actually
taking care of my family that's not
healthy if I'm just watching Netflix all
day that's not healthy that's not going
to get me to where I want to go
go but we have so much available to us
today that we didn't before and AI can
also be a tool to do this where we put
our thought Focus starts to manifest in
our actions in our lives we start to do
things again we might not be doing the
thing that we're watching on the
television but I'll tell you you know
they've done studies and researches if
that's all that somebody fills
themselves up
with they got to be careful where
they stop recognizing what's the
difference between reality and what's
fiction in your
business there's a powerful way you can
you can tune your reticulating
activating your reticular activating
system by adjusting what you're focusing
on throughout the day and then this is
where consistency comes in in your
marketing one of the biggest mistakes
that I notice that people make in their
marketing is they're posting about a lot
of different things Gary vaynerchuck
gave this advice about a lot of
different things posting a lot of
different stuff on social media years
back and I understand it from the
beginning sense to see which one starts
to stick with people but then you want
to really focus in on where's that
alignment that's going to start to bring
in sales for me what are the people that
are going to buy for me what do they
really want for me people they want to
know how to build their landing pages
how to get more clients and how to do
that and so what I then have to look at
is okay I'm going to be start to be
consistent because every time somebody
starts associating my name that they see
on social media they should be
associating that with a certain outcome
that they can
expect getting more clients with their
marketing with their advertising with
their landing pages that's exactly what
I'm known for that's exactly what I help
people do day in and day out to be able
to optimize this and and and I hear
often from people that they've never had
success
before in their business and they come
into my ecosystem and things start to
fall into place I'd love to encourage
you by the way to jump into one of our
trainings that we have over at my
website jeremi ky.com to jump into my
client growth accelerator when we have
enrollment open for that program you
know at the time of this recording
there'll be a waiting list for that but
we'll be opening it up we open it up a
couple times a year as far as that go so
stay tuned for those possibilities stay
tuned for when I'm running
advertisements across social media
you'll see my name come across the ads
as far as that goes go follow my
Instagram go follow my Facebook page so
why would I tell you to do that because
what's going to happen is and this is a
great part of marketing and by the way
you can plug in and actually watch How I
Market my coaching business you can
observe exactly what I do to get clients
and then model it and use it as a model
in your business and I I can walk you
through step by step all of those
processes and that's exactly what we do
on this YouTube channel so make sure
that you
subscribe is that when somebody sees an
ad that you run and then they see
another one and another one you start to
build name recognition and brand
awareness in the minds of people as the
consistent person that solves the ever
pressing problem that they have I meet
people all the time they have an never
pressing problem of getting clients in
their business and it's been bugging
them for two two to 5 years and they've
not done anything about it and then they
see me show up couple times a week
giving Solutions in these areas and now
they start to say let me check out a
training that Jeremiah has and then they
join my coaching program and then they
start to get
results and so for you how do you apply
this in your business I want you to
figure out what is the ever pressing
problem that's in the front of the
reticular activating system for your
target client what is the thing that
they just ruminate about like crazy and
they just cannot get over what causes
them to lose sleep at night what
frustrates them more than anything else
I want you to think about this as a
business owner if you're a coach if
you're a mentor if you're a trainer and
you're trying to get clients or you have
an e-commerce business or you're trying
to build an influencer brand or you're
trying to be an author or a speaker or
sell courses or sell just about anything
there's a problem that what you sell
solves business is built on solving
problems even
entertainment entertainment helps
distract people from the pain that
they're dealing with and it also helps
again align their energy in certain ways
the way that I use entertainment solves
a problem everything solves a problem
that has finances attached to it money
is a transfer of energy to solve
problems and so what you do in business
is you are a solutionist that is selling
the result and the end outcome to a
problem that people
have and so what you want to identify is
what is the main problem the people that
are going to spend the most amount of
money with
you and this is where we got to
challenge ourselves because I notice and
I know people do this well I want to
help
everybody but there's a certain group of
people that's going to spend more money
with you and you want to really really
focus your energy on that group you want
to put all your focus in on that group
that comes to you for that problem to be
solved they're asking you for that they
they they would they would
move Heaven and Earth to have you solve
that one problem again for me most
people it's Facebook ads it's their
marketing it's their funnels is why they
come to me for that it's a how to get
more clients when things stagnate for
them that's what I'm known for that's
what my reputation has become and that's
what I've done for 21 years is help
people get more clients
and again whatever you become known for
if you look at your whole body of work
of your life your experiences how you
help people how you work with
people it could look different any any
which way as far as that goes so what I
want you to understand is this is that
when you can learn to become very very
specific about the problems that you
solve you can start to articulate those
to people and you can start to
communicate those to people people and
then as you start to communicate those
to
people people start to recognize it and
they start to say and make decisions and
say I want to move forward in working
with you and then that's how you get
paid and you get to accelerate this
process which is really really cool
that's why my coaching program is called
the client growth accelerator is to
speed up that process to help you to be
able to fi to create Financial Freedom
by by getting consistent with your
messaging with your marketing with your
sales to be able to dial in all of the
different things and simplify them so
that you're not overwhelmed and so that
you start to get results
fast flip that to what you're doing in
your
business how do you help people get
results
fast maybe you might be watching the
saying I don't know how I help people
get results fast you got to believing in
yourself more you got to start believing
in the possibilities more to not doubt
ourselves and grow in the skill of
whatever you lack whatever you feel like
I need a skill of one of the number one
things learn to become articulate and
how you talk on camera and being able to
communicate on video with people the art
and skill of being able to communicate
on video with people which by the way I
did I struggled with for years I didn't
know how to communicate on video at all
years ago had no clue and I've come up
with Frameworks to be able to do so I
think I do pretty well I've come up with
Frameworks to even do so without without
notes where I actually can trigger my
mind and my own reticular activating
system to operate out of my intuition to
be able to teach and articulate Concepts
to people that are very simple and easy
to understand and to simplify them in as
few words as possible one of the best
ways that you can successfully help
people is to not overe explain things
but to keep it
simple and if they want more details
they can ask later things will start to
stand out to you to them when you do
that and that's where your lane of
marketing is as you figure out what
stands out what is the
pattern and you actually get into a
connective
conversation with the people that you
are marketing to where they will tell
you in their own words EX exactly what
they need help with and then what you do
is you take that feedback and you
reverse engineer that we use artificial
intelligence to help us do this into
creating offers and products exactly
based on what the needs of the market
for are as well as brainstorming new
ideas that maybe the market didn't ask
us by bringing our knowledge and our
experience into and combining it with
the feedback loop that we receive and
that feedback loop is one of the best
ways to Succeed in Business one of the
ways that we do this is we use
transcripts we take the transcripts of
people when they're in our coaching
calls when they're in our training calls
when they're on our Q&A calls I take the
questions that are posted on my social
media and I filter them into I have a
document over 200 pages of answers from
people as to what their ever pressing
problems are and it all boils down to
this marketing Facebook ads getting more
clients through their
funnels you know the basics of a funnel
they understand but when it comes to
actually what is an award-winning funnel
that's actually going to produce results
what's actually going to make six seven
and eight
figures that's hard for
people and so for you you got to figure
out what is
your specific
area that stands
out that's like a pink elephant that's
like a yellow
submarine that stands
out to reach the people that you're
looking to
reach you have to stand out and one of
the biggest areas that I notice that
people struggle with is they're trying
to play small they're trying to play it
safe and they're trying to hide behind
the scenes and they're trying to not be
seen and not be heard and they've been
told their whole life to not be seen and
not be heard and they don't feel like
they have permission to have a voice and
they don't want to be too big and they
don't want to have too big of
energy and and that becomes the cycle of
how they operate that's how I operated
for years how do I stay behind the
scenes how do I not push the envelope
too far how do I stay safe and play it
safe and not take
risks can I tell you this the greatest
risk that you can take is trying to stay
safe and play it
safe one of the best decisions that you
can make is to start to step out and be
willing to do something that you've
never done before be willing to try
something that you've never done before
be willing to jump in with both feet
into the deep end and realize you might
not know how to swim but you'll figure
it out and when you have somebody like a
coach or a mentor which is exactly what
I do with people to come alongside with
you to walk you through that process and
to help support you and guide you and
direct you through the hard stuff you
won't
sink and that's exactly what you are to
your clients people are looking for a
swimming coach
in their specific area that you Mentor
people in they don't want to sink they
don't want to drown they want somebody
that can hold them afloat as they learn
as they grow you know I got a one and a
half-year-old son he's learning he's
growing he's learning to do hard things
he takes risks Mommy and Daddy got to
help direct him when you are a coach or
a mentor you do the same thing that we
do with children with your clients I
think that's one of the biggest things
that we miss is actually realizing that
really a lot of times when we're
coaching people it's an underdeveloped
area of their understanding that we have
to start at the very Baseline level and
help people understand how to go from
where they are to where they want to be
and by the way that's respect that's
honoring where somebody is at it's
dishonor to have to sound smart and
posture ourselves as somebody that knows
more than we really
do or knows exactly what we know in
order to validate ourselves I'm not
trying to get validation from people and
I don't care if we got haters that
aren't even the people I'm trying to
reach that say well you're you're
keeping stuff too simple it's too it's
not logical enough it's
not all this negativity I don't focus on
it I focus in on who are the people that
I help
consistently and I expect that the
people that are in my space that are
watching my content are wanting the
results that we deliver
and I start to believe and I start to
have faith and I start to understand
that I may not see it right now but I
start to have faith for where I'm going
and the fact that people will come
because they resonate with the words and
the language and the energy that I'm
putting
across and I'm able to do so with
confidence with
Charisma even in areas where I don't
have evidence even in in areas where I'm
just starting out and training yourself
to be able to do that to be able to put
yourself out there with confidence to
not shrink back in unknown situations to
not let the fear of the unknown run your
life and to actually not let fear decide
your choices so often we let what we're
afraid of happening decide what we're
going to do
what if you let what you're hoping
happens
decide well I don't want to get
disappointed we work so stinking hard to
avoid
disappointment when all disappointment
is is just a madeup feeling in our mind
and our bodies that yes I get it maybe
you felt it for a long time don't
understand I don't mean any disrespect
by this but it's a thought and it's a
feeling and disappointment is literally
a construct of our minds based and
experiences of the pain that we want to
feel yes grieve yes you will feel
sometimes disappointment but then learn
to ground yourself and move on quickly
and get back up again and become
resilient and resist the urge to dwell
on the past memories and the mistakes
and the things that didn't work out for
you to start to move things forward in a
positive direction just to start
to move move the needle forward for
where you're
going you know we can get really stuck
focusing on what's not
working we can get really stuck looking
at what needs to change in our
lives what if you started paying
attention to what has worked out and you
started doing more of that
consistently our brain starts going
crazy saying well last time that
happened then bad stuff happened and
you know I bought this house and then I
lost everything it's like come on what
if you focused on the good what if you
focused on the goodness what if you
became intentional to do
that and you started putting your mind
focus on how things will work out for
you what if they do work out then
what and
realize that we end up talking ourselves
out of our dreams and our vision because
we're so afraid
of them not working out our need to
control everything starts to dominate
everything that we do our need and
desire to make things go our way and I
again I don't mean any disrespect by
this especially if you've experienced
abuse or pain or trauma or people that
have hurt you before I understand you
need to have boundaries I get
it but it takes letting go of control in
your life and surrendering to the
process and saying okay what's next for
me I say a prayer and I say God put some
Supernatural on top of my natural
ability and I'm amazed what happens when
I pray things start to fall into place
things start to come into alignment when
something's not working out I pray and I
say God give me wisdom in this
area and no matter what your faith is
your or or what you do believe in put
your faith in something put your faith
in yourself if you have
to you know without having faith without
having belief what are we actually
stepping
towards we're just shooting in the dark
we're just essentially gambling and we
become addicted to the slot machine
sometimes it works out but most of the
time it doesn't because we become
addicted to the possibility of things
happening for us and we don't actually
want things to go well for us because it
would be different and we would start to
worry that things would go bad after the
good happens just like a slot machine it
literally becomes addictive in our
minds it does it's an addictive pattern
that we get into and when you break
it you got to control where your
thoughts are
going you got to control where your
energy is going where are you putting
your focus and start to focus your
energy on what's going to move the
needle forward for
you what's going to get you those
clients what's going to get people
showing up in your space what's going to
get people coming into your EC system
and deciding to work with
you maybe you don't know what that is
again I'd love to help you with that we
can identify that very quickly with
artificial intelligence by understanding
what are the problem s that people have
and what are their desires and then
creating a bridge between their problem
and the solution and you run a business
where you charge money to get people
from point A to point B that's what
business
is and I'd love to help you to start to
move that thing forward for you so to
start to move the forward momentum and
to start to get it going for you even if
it things have never worked out for you
before even if you've tried everything
that there is and you've listened to
every Guru there is on the planet you
know I wouldn't call myself a guru but
I've had people say that I'm like the
guru to the gurus I've had people call
me that for
years because I can look at a situation
I can say oh wait let's change this two
or three things and then it just starts
to work and it starts to produce money
and starts to be profitable I'd love to
help you with that as well again jump
into my client growth accelerator
program when we have enrollment open to
that and let's help you start to succeed
we'll talk soon everybody have a good
one